Guide to the Oregonian photographs collection circa 1850-1984
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Subjects, circa 1850-1983; circa 1910-1983; Series H
  - Branding Irons (Box-folder 94/12)
  - Bricks and Brickmaking (Box-folder 94/13)
  - Brides (Box-folder 94/14)
    Photographs of bridal shows and consultants.
  - Briquets (Box-folder 94/15)
  - Brooms (Box-folder 94/16)
  - Brotherhood Week (Box-folder 94/17)
  - Buckets (Box-folder 94/18)
  - Buddhists (Box-folder 94/19)
  - Budgeting (Box-folder 94/20)
  - Building Collapses (Box-folder 94/21)
  - Building Comparison Chart, 1969 November (Box-folder 94/22)
    Chart showing the comparative costs, sizes and occupancies of several Portland buildings, including Crown Plaza, the First National Bank Building, and the Georgia-Pacific Building.
  - Building Demolition (Box-folder 94/23)
  - Building Materials (Box-folder 94/24)
  - Building Moving (Box-folder 94/25)
  - Buildings (Box-folder 94/26)
  - Bumper Stickers (Box-folder 94/27)
  - "Bundles for Britain" Program (Box-folder 94/28)
  - Bunker Hill Mining Co. (Box-folder 94/29)
  - Burglary (Box-folder 94/30)
  - Burls (Box-folder 94/31)
  - Burn Victims (Children) (Box-folder 94/32)
    Originally filed under "Burns" or "Burned Children."
  - Bus Drivers (Box-folder 94/33)
  - Buttons (Box-folder 95/1)
  - Cabins (Box-folder 95/2)
  - Cabinets (Box-folder 95/3)
  - Caissons (Box-folder 95/4)
  - Calculators (Box-folder 95/5)
  - Calendars (Box-folder 95/6)
  - Cameras (Box-folder 95/7)
  - Campgrounds (Box-folder 95/8)
    See also: Sports and Recreation - Camping.
  - Candleholders (Box-folder 95/9)
  - Candles (Box-folder 95/10)
  - Car Thefts (Box-folder 95/11)
  - Cars and Other Motor Vehicles, Subseries 5
    - Abandoned Vehicles (Box-folder 95/12)
    - Ambulances (Box-folder 95/13)
    - Amphibious Vehicles (Box-folder 95/14)
    - Antique and Early Cars (1) (Box-folder 95/15)
    - Antique and Early Cars (2) (Box-folder 95/16)
    - Armored Cars (Box-folder 95/17)
    - Auto Shows (Box-folder 95/18)
    - Bookmobiles (Box-folder 95/19)
    - Bulldozers (Box-folder 95/20)
    - Bus Accidents (Box-folder 95/21)
    - Bus Trips (Box-folder 95/22)
    - Buses (Box-folder 95/23)
    - Cable Cars (Box-folder 95/24)
    - Campers (Box-folder 95/25)
    - Car Accidents (1) (Box-folder 95/26)
    - Car Accidents (2) (Box-folder 96/1)
    - Car Accidents - Hit-and-Run (Box-folder 96/2)
    - Car Accidents - Elder Family, 1970 June (Box-folder 96/3)
      Hood River County family whose car went into the Columbia River, killing all family members.
    - Car Dealers (Box-folder 96/4)
    - Car Parts (Box-folder 96/5)
    - Car Repairs (Box-folder 96/6)
    - Car Safety (Box-folder 96/7)
    - Car Trips (Box-folder 96/8)
    - Cars - General (1) (Box-folder 96/9)
    - Cars - General (2) (Box-folder 96/10)
    - Dune Buggies (Box-folder 96/11)
    - Electric Vehicles (Box-folder 96/12)
    - Emissions and Fuel Economy Testing (Box-folder 96/13)
    - Fire Engines and Trucks (Box-folder 96/14)
    - Garbage Trucks (Box-folder 96/15)
    - Homemade Cars (Box-folder 96/16)
    - Hot Rods (Box-folder 96/17)
    - Jeeps (Box-folder 96/18)
    - License and Registration (Box-folder 96/19)
      Includes photographs of license plates.
    - Lift Trucks (Box-folder 96/20)
      Also known as forklifts
    - "Marne Taxi" (Box-folder 97/1)
      1909 Renault that was used at the Battle of the Marne.
    - Motorcycle Accidents (Box-folder 97/2)
    - Motorcycle Trips (Box-folder 97/3)
    - Motorcycles (Box-folder 97/4)
    - "Popcorn Wagon" (Box-folder 97/5)
      1928 Overland Whippet used by Arthur ("Frenchy") du Frense, who sold treats to schoolchildren.
    - School Bus Accidents (Box-folder 97/6)
    - School Buses (Box-folder 97/7)
    - Straddle Trucks (Box-folder 97/8)
    - Trucks (Box-folder 97/9)
      Includes 1921 and 1926 photographs of Oregonian delivery trucks.
    - Test Driving (Box-folder 97/10)
    - Wrecking Yards (Box-folder 97/11)
  - Car Washes (Box-folder 97/12)
  - Carousels (Box-folder 97/13)
    Also known as merry-go-rounds.
  - Carpenters (Box-folder 97/14)
  - Carpets (Box-folder 97/15)
  - Carpooling (Box-folder 97/16)
  - Carports (Box-folder 97/17)
  - Cash Registers (Box-folder 97/18)
  - Catapults (Box-folder 97/19)
  - Cattle Rustling (Box-folder 97/20)
  - Cave-Ins (Box-folder 97/21)
  - Cemeteries (Box-folder 97/22)
    Photographs of cemeteries whose location was unspecified.
  - Census (Box-folder 97/23)
  - Central African Republic Citizens (Box-folder 97/24)
  - Certificates (Box-folder 97/25)
  - Chafing Dish (Box-folder 97/26)
  - Chain Letters (Box-folder 97/27)
  - Chains (Box-folder 97/28)
  - Chainsaws (Box-folder 97/29)
  - Chairs (Box-folder 97/30)
  - Charcoal (Box-folder 97/31)
  - Check Sorters (Box-folder 97/32)
  - Checks (Box-folder 97/33)
  - Cherry Blossoms (Box-folder 97/34)
    Photographs pairing young women and cherry blossoms.
  - Child Abandonment (Box-folder 97/35)
  - Child Abuse (Box-folder 97/36)
  - Child Care (Box-folder 98/1)
    Includes photographs of child care centers outside of Portland.
  - Child Custody (Box-folder 98/2)
  - Child Development (Box-folder 98/3)
  - Child Safety (Box-folder 98/4)
  - Childbirth (Box-folder 98/5)
  - Children (1) (Box-folder 98/6)
  - Children (2) (Box-folder 98/7)
  - Children's Day Camps (Box-folder 98/8)
  - Chimney Sweeps (Box-folder 98/9)
  - Chimneys (Box-folder 98/10)
  - Chinese Dragon (Box-folder 98/11)
  - Chorus Lines (Box-folder 98/12)
  - Christmas Cards (Box-folder 98/13)
  - Christmas Decorations (Box-folder 98/14)
  - Christmas Lights (Box-folder 98/15)
  - Christmas Shopping (Box-folder 98/16)
  - Christmas Trees (Box-folder 98/17)
  - Chukar Coops (Box-folder 98/18)
  - Cigarettes (Box-folder 98/19)
  - Cigars (Box-folder 98/20)
  - Cinnamon Bear (Box-folder 98/21)
  - Cisterns (Box-folder 98/22)
  - Citizens Band Radio (Box-folder 98/23)
  - Civilian Conservation Coprs (CCC) (Box-folder 98/24)
  - Clocks (1) (Box-folder 98/25)
  - Clocks (2) (Box-folder 99/1)
  - Clothing Drives (Box-folder 99/2)
  - Cloud Seeding (Box-folder 99/3)
  - Clouds (Box-folder 99/4)
  - Cobalt (Box-folder 99/5)
  - Coffee Grinders (Box-folder 99/6)
  - Coins (Box-folder 99/7)
  - Collection Plate (Box-folder 99/8)
    Found in folder with images related to Bishop Scott House, St. Stephens Chapel and early Portland schools. Folder label read in part, "Famous collection plate (Where is it now?)"
  - Collections and Collectors (Box-folder 99/9)
  - Comets (Box-folder 99/10)
  - Comic Books (Box-folder 99/11)
  - Communes (Box-folder 99/12)
  - Computers (Box-folder 99/13)
  - Concrete (Box-folder 99/14)
  - Concrete Cones (Box-folder 99/15)
  - Concrete Houses (Box-folder 99/16)
  - Confiscated Weapons (Box-folder 99/17)
  - Conscientious Objectors (Box-folder 99/18)
  - Construction (Box-folder 99/19)
  - Cornerstones (Box-folder 99/20)
  - Corsages (Box-folder 99/21)
  - Costa Rican People (Box-folder 99/22)
  - Costumes (Box-folder 99/23)
  - Cotillion Balls (Box-folder 99/24)
  - Counterfeiting (Box-folder 99/25)
  - Coupons (Box-folder 99/26)
  - Courtroom Photography (Box-folder 99/27)
  - Covered Bridges (Box-folder 100/1)
  - Covered Wagons (Box-folder 100/2)
  - Cowboy Hats (Box-folder 100/3)
  - Cowboys and Cowgirls (Box-folder 100/4)
  - Cradleboards (Box-folder 100/5)
  - Cranes (Box-folder 100/6)
  - Credit Cards (Box-folder 100/7)
  - Credit Unions (Box-folder 100/8)
  - Crime Maps (Box-folder 100/9)
  - Crime Prevention and Detection (Box-folder 100/10)
  - Criminal Identification (Box-folder 100/11)
  - Crosses (Box-folder 100/12)
  - Crown-Zellerback Corp. (Box-folder 100/13)
  - Crowns (Box-folder 100/14)
  - Crusade for Freedom (Box-folder 100/15)
  - Crystals (Box-folder 100/16)
  - Curfew Alarms (Box-folder 100/17)
  - Curtains (Box-folder 100/18)
  - Dairy Family of the Year (Box-folder 100/19)
  - Dating (Box-folder 100/20)
  - Day Care (Box-folder 100/21)
  - Daylight Savings Time (Box-folder 100/22)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls (Box-folder 100/23)
  - Deaf People (Box-folder 100/24)
  - Declaration of Independence (Box-folder 100/25)
  - Decoys (Box-folder 100/26)
  - Deeds (Box-folder 100/27)
  - Demonstrations (Box-folder 100/28)
  - Demonstrations - Bonus Army March (Box-folder 100/29)
    Protest by World War I veterans in Washington, D.C. which was led by Portlander W. W. Walters.
  - Deportation (Box-folder 100/30)
  - Diamonds (Box-folder 100/31)
  - Diapers (Box-folder 100/32)
  - Diaries (Box-folder 101/1)
    Contains image of two pages from John C. Young's diary, written during the War of 1812.
  - Diets (Box-folder 101/2)
  - Dikes (Box-folder 101/3)
  - Dirt Houses (Box-folder 101/4)
  - "Disasters, 1900-1950" (Box-folder 101/5)
    Series of images published for Pictorial News Annual issue in 1950 depicting various disasters, including one of the Vanport flood. See Written Materials series for published piece.
  - Dishes (Box-folder 101/6)
  - Dog Houses (Box-folder 101/7)
  - Doors (Box-folder 101/8)
  - Douglas Aircraft Company, Inc. (Box-folder 101/9)
    Photographs showing the manufacture of aircraft in the company's Santa Monica, California factory.
  - Doukhobor Sect (Box-folder 101/10)
    Canadian religious group, a radical offshoot of which committed acts of arson.
  - Dredging (Box-folder 101/11)
  - Driftwood (Box-folder 101/12)
  - Drills (Box-folder 101/13)
  - Drownings (Box-folder 101/14)
  - Drunk Tests (Box-folder 101/15)
  - Dry Cleaning (Box-folder 101/16)
  - Dry Ice (Box-folder 101/17)
  - "Dry Land Sailboat" (Box-folder 101/18)
    Wheeled contraption attached to sail built by two Maupin residents.
  - Drydocks (Box-folder 101/19)
  - Dude Ranches (Box-folder 101/20)
  - Dutch People (Box-folder 101/21)
  - Dynamite (Box-folder 101/22)
  - Eagle Scouts (Box-folder 101/23)
  - Earrings (Box-folder 101/24)
  - Earth Movers (Box-folder 101/25)
  - Earthquakes (Box-folder 101/26)
  - Earthquake Recording Equipment (Box-folder 101/27)
  - Easter Eggs (Box-folder 101/28)
  - Eastern Star (Box-folder 101/29)
  - Eclipses (Box-folder 101/30)
  - Education, Subseries 6
    - Apprenticeships (Box-folder 101/31)
    - Aptitude Tests (Box-folder 101/32)
    - Audio-Visual Aids (Box-folder 101/33)
    - Business-Industry Education Day (Box-folder 101/34)
    - Career Education (Box-folder 101/35)
    - Charm School (Box-folder 101/36)
    - College Enrollment Projections, 1968 (Box-folder 101/37)
    - Cooking School (Box-folder 101/38)
    - Drivers' Education (Box-folder 101/39)
    - Educational Television (Box-folder 102/1)
    - English as a Second Language (ESL) (Box-folder 102/2)
    - Exchange Students (Box-folder 102/3)
      Photographs of both Oregonians studying abroad and of students in Oregon from other parts of the United States.
    - Flood Control Classes (Box-folder 102/4)
    - Foreign Students (1) (Box-folder 102/5)
    - Foreign Students (2) (Box-folder 102/6)
    - Gifted Students (Box-folder 102/7)
    - Graduation Ceremonies (Box-folder 102/8)
    - Head Start Program (Box-folder 102/9)
    - Home Economics (Box-folder 102/10)
    - Kindergarten (Box-folder 102/11)
    - Learning Disabilities (Box-folder 102/12)
    - Mathematics (Box-folder 102/13)
    - Mountain Climbing School (Box-folder 102/14)
    - Scholarships and Fellowships (Box-folder 102/15)
    - Students (Box-folder 102/16)
      Contains images of both high school and college students.
    - Teachers and Administrators (Box-folder 102/17)
      Mostly group photographs taken at educational conferences
    - Test Score Rankings (Box-folder 102/18)
  - Effigies (Box-folder 102/19)
  - Electric Appliances (Box-folder 102/20)
  - Electric Chairs (Box-folder 102/21)
  - Electric Circuit Breakers (Box-folder 102/22)
  - Electric Lighting (Box-folder 103/1)
  - Electrical Panels (Box-folder 103/2)
  - Elevator Operators (Box-folder 103/3)
  - Elevators (Box-folder 103/4)
  - Emblems (Box-folder 103/5)
    See also: Subjects - Insignias.
  - Emergency Services (Box-folder 103/6)
  - Emotionally Distrubed Children (Box-folder 103/7)
  - Employment (Box-folder 103/8)
  - Energy, Subseries 7
    - Conservation (Box-folder 103/9)
    - Electric Generators (Box-folder 103/10)
    - Federal Power Commission Hearing, 1963 June 6 (Box-folder 103/11)
      Hearing regarding Idaho Power Co.'s plans for a dam on the Snake River
    - Fuel Shotages (Box-folder 103/12)
    - Gas Pipelines (Box-folder 103/13)
    - Gas Wells (Box-folder 103/14)
    - Gasoline (Box-folder 103/15)
    - Geothermal Leases Map, circa 1980 (Box-folder 103/16)
      Hand-drawn map showing the area where the Lamar Hunt family's leases near Crump Lake.
    - Geothermal Power (Box-folder 103/17)
    - Oil Wells (Box-folder 103/18)
  - Engines (Box-folder 103/19)
  - Evictions (Box-folder 103/20)
  - Evidence (Box-folder 103/21)
  - Ex-Convicts (Box-folder 103/22)
  - Excavations (Box-folder 103/23)
  - Exhibits (Box-folder 103/24)
    Undated photographs depicting exhibit rooms. Includes what are labeled as "Educational Exhibit" and "Oregon Woods Exhibit," as well as a display of Salem cherries.
  - Expeditions (Box-folder 103/25)
  - Explosions (Box-folder 103/26)
  - Extradition (Box-folder 103/27)
  - Eyeglasses (Box-folder 103/28)
  - Factory Workers (Box-folder 103/29)
    Two undated photographs of workers in an unidentified factory.
  - Fairs and Festivals (Box-folder 103/30)
  - Families (Box-folder 103/31)
  - Family Counseling Services (Box-folder 103/32)
  - Family Trees (Box-folder 103/33)
  - Fans (Box-folder 103/34)
  - Fashion (Box-folder 103/35)
  - Fathers (Box-folder 103/36)
  - Feed Sacks (Box-folder 104/1)
  - Feed Stores (Box-folder 104/2)
  - Fences (Box-folder 104/3)
  - Fiberglass (Box-folder 104/4)
  - Fingerprints (Box-folder 104/5)
  - Finnish-American People (Box-folder 104/6)
  - Fire Alarms (Box-folder 104/7)
  - Fire Escapes (Box-folder 104/8)
  - Fire Hydrants (Box-folder 104/9)
  - Fire Prevention and Safety (Box-folder 104/10)
  - Firefighters and Firefighting (1) (Box-folder 104/11)
    See also: Subjects - Forest Fires and Firefighting.
  - Firefighters and Firefighting (2) (Box-folder 104/12)
  - Fireplaces (Box-folder 104/13)
  - Fireworks (Box-folder 104/14)
  - Fish Ladders (Box-folder 104/15)
  - Fishing, Subseries 8
    See also: Boats and Other Watercraft - Fishing Boats
    - General (1) (Box-folder 104/16)
    - General (2) (Box-folder 104/17)
    - General (3) (Box-folder 104/18)
    - General (4) (Box-folder 104/19)
    - Bass (Box-folder 104/20)
    - Catfish (Box-folder 104/21)
    - Clams (Box-folder 104/22)
      See also: Sports and Recreation - Clam-Digging
    - Crabs (Box-folder 105/1)
    - Crappies (Box-folder 105/2)
    - Crawfish (Box-folder 105/3)
    - Equipment (Box-folder 105/4)
    - Fish Hatcheries (Box-folder 105/5)
    - Fish Wheels (Box-folder 105/6)
    - Halibut (Box-folder 105/7)
    - Marlins (Box-folder 105/8)
    - Octopi (Box-folder 105/9)
  - Flags (1) (Box-folder 105/10)
  - Flags (2) (Box-folder 105/11)
  - Flags (3) (Box-folder 105/12)
  - Flea Markets (Box-folder 105/13)
  - Flea Research (Box-folder 105/14)
    Contains photographs of laboratories for studying fleas at Pacific University and in Crane, Oregon.
  - Flood Control (Box-folder 105/15)
  - Floods (Box-folder 105/16)
  - Floods - Columbia River, 1948 June (Box-folder 105/17)
    Series of aerial photos taken of the 1948 flood's effects in Oregon and Washington.
    See also: Oregon - Floods - Vanport (May-June 1948); Portland - Floods - May-June 1948.
  - Flora and Fauna, Subseries 9
    Includes images related to extinct and mythical creatures. For photographs of cows, see: Agriculture - Cattle.
    See also: Portland - Washington Park Zoo.
    - Aardvarks (Box-folder 106/1)
    - Albatrosses (Box-folder 106/2)
    - Alligators (Box-folder 106/3)
    - Anchovies (Box-folder 106/4)
    - Antelopes (Box-folder 106/5)
    - Ants (Box-folder 106/6)
    - Apes (Box-folder 106/7)
    - Baboons (Box-folder 106/8)
    - Badgers (Box-folder 106/9)
    - Banana Plants (Box-folder 106/10)
    - Bats (Box-folder 106/11)
    - Bears (Box-folder 106/12)
    - Beavers (Box-folder 106/13)
    - Bees (Box-folder 106/14)
    - Beetles (Box-folder 106/15)
    - Bigfoot (Box-folder 106/16)
      Also known as Sasquatch.
    - Birds (Unspecified) (Box-folder 106/17)
    - Bitterns (Box-folder 106/18)
    - Blackbirds (Box-folder 106/19)
    - Blossoms (Box-folder 106/20)
    - Bluebirds (Box-folder 106/21)
    - Bluejays (Box-folder 106/22)
    - Bobcats (Box-folder 106/23)
    - Buffalo (Box-folder 106/24)
      Also known as bison.
    - Burros (Box-folder 106/25)
    - Butterflies (Box-folder 106/26)
    - Buzzards (Box-folder 106/27)
    - Cacti (Box-folder 106/28)
    - Camels (Box-folder 106/29)
    - Carp (Box-folder 106/30)
    - Caterpillars (Box-folder 106/31)
    - Cats (Box-folder 106/32)
    - Cedar Waxwings (Box-folder 106/33)
    - Chameleons (Box-folder 106/34)
    - Cheetahs (Box-folder 106/35)
    - Chickens (Box-folder 106/36)
    - Chimpanzees (Box-folder 106/37)
    - Chinchillas (Box-folder 107/1)
    - Chipmunks (Box-folder 107/2)
    - Chukars (Box-folder 107/3)
    - Civet Cats (Box-folder 107/4)
    - Clams (Box-folder 107/5)
    - Coatimundi (Box-folder 107/6)
    - Cockroaches (Box-folder 107/7)
    - Condors (Box-folder 107/8)
    - Cougars (Box-folder 107/9)
    - Coyotes (Box-folder 107/10)
    - Crabs (Box-folder 107/11)
    - Cranes (Box-folder 107/12)
    - Crawfish (Box-folder 107/13)
    - Crickets (Box-folder 107/14)
    - Crows (Box-folder 107/15)
    - Cutworms (Box-folder 107/16)
    - Daffofils (Box-folder 107/17)
    - Deer (Box-folder 107/18)
    - Dogs (1) (Box-folder 107/19)
    - Dogs (2) (Box-folder 107/20)
    - Dogs (3) (Box-folder 107/21)
    - Dogwood Trees (Box-folder 107/22)
    - Dolphins (Box-folder 107/23)
    - Donkeys (Box-folder 107/24)
    - Dragonflies (Box-folder 107/25)
    - Ducks (Box-folder 107/26)
    - Eagles (Box-folder 108/1)
    - Earwigs (Box-folder 108/2)
    - Elephants (Box-folder 108/3)
      See also: Portland - Washington Park Zoo - Elephants
    - Elephants - Tusko (Box-folder 108/4)
      Circus elephant that appeared in Portland.
    - Elk (Box-folder 108/5)
    - Evergreens (Box-folder 108/6)
    - Falcons (Box-folder 108/7)
    - Ferrets (Box-folder 108/8)
    - Fish (Unspecified) (Box-folder 108/9)
    - Flamingos (Box-folder 108/10)
    - Flies (Box-folder 108/11)
    - Flowers (Box-folder 108/12)
      Contains photographs of various flowers taken by Irving Penn.
      See Written Materials series for press release that accompanied prints.
    - Four-Leaf Clovers (Box-folder 108/12)
    - Foxes (Box-folder 108/13)
    - Frogs (Box-folder 108/14)
    - Fruit Flies (Box-folder 108/15)
    - Fuchsias (Box-folder 108/16)
    - Fungi (Box-folder 108/17)
      Includes photographs originally labeled "Mushrooms."
    - Geese (Box-folder 108/18)
    - Gibbons (Box-folder 108/19)
    - Giraffes (Box-folder 108/20)
    - Goats (Box-folder 108/21)
    - Golden Pheasants (Box-folder 108/22)
    - Gorse (Box-folder 108/23)
    - Grass (Box-folder 108/24)
    - Grasshoppers (Box-folder 108/25)
    - Groundhogs (Box-folder 109/1)
    - Hamsters (Box-folder 109/2)
    - Hawks (Box-folder 109/3)
    - Hippopotami (Box-folder 109/4)
    - Holly (Box-folder 109/5)
    - Horses (Box-folder 109/6)
    - Hummingbirds (Box-folder 109/7)
    - Iguanas (Box-folder 109/8)
    - Insects (Unspecified) (Box-folder 109/9)
    - Jaguars (Box-folder 109/10)
    - Jellyfish (Box-folder 109/11)
    - Kinkajous (Box-folder 109/12)
    - Lambs (Box-folder 109/13)
    - Lampreys (Box-folder 109/14)
    - Leaves (Box-folder 109/15)
    - Leeches (Box-folder 109/16)
    - Lemurs (Box-folder 109/17)
    - Leopards (Box-folder 109/18)
    - Lions (Box-folder 109/19)
    - Llamas (Box-folder 109/20)
    - Lynxes (Box-folder 109/21)
    - Macaws (Box-folder 109/22)
    - Magpies (Box-folder 109/23)
    - Marmosets (Box-folder 109/24)
    - Mice (Box-folder 109/25)
    - Ming Trees (Box-folder 109/26)
    - Moles (Box-folder 109/27)
    - Monkeys (Box-folder 109/28)
    - Moose (Box-folder 109/29)
    - Mosquitos (Box-folder 109/30)
    - Moss (Box-folder 109/31)
    - Moths (Box-folder 109/32)
    - Mules (Box-folder 109/33)
    - Murre (Box-folder 110/1)
    - Musk Oxen (Box-folder 110/2)
    - Muskrats (Box-folder 110/3)
    - Mynahs (Box-folder 110/4)
    - Nematodes (Box-folder 110/5)
    - Peacocks (Box-folder 110/6)
    - Peccaries (Box-folder 110/7)
    - Pigs (Box-folder 110/8)
    - Pine Trees (Box-folder 110/9)
    - Robins (Box-folder 110/10)
    - Seagulls (Box-folder 110/11)
    - Sheep (Box-folder 110/12)
    - Starlings (Box-folder 110/13)
    - Swallows (Box-folder 110/14)
    - Swans (Box-folder 110/15)
  - Florists (Box-folder 110/16)
  - Flower Arrangments (Box-folder 110/17)
  - Flower Mining (Box-folder 110/18)
    Photograph of gold panners retouched so that it looks as though they are panning for flowers. Used for an August 18 1963 gardening article.
  - Foam House, 1972 (Box-folder 110/19)
    Project undertaken by University of Oregon students.
  - Food and Beverage, Subseries 10
    - General (Box-folder 110/20)
    - Bakeries (Box-folder 110/21)
    - Barbecues (Box-folder 110/22)
    - Bars (Box-folder 110/23)
    - Beer (Box-folder 110/24)
    - Bread (Box-folder 110/25)
    - Butter (Box-folder 110/26)
    - Buttermilk (Box-folder 110/27)
    - Cakes (Box-folder 110/28)
    - Candy (Box-folder 110/29)
    - Cheese (Box-folder 110/30)
    - Chefs (Box-folder 111/1)
    - Cherry Square Desserts, 1979 February (Box-folder 111/2)
      Originally filed under "metric system" because the recipes had used metric measurements
    - Cider (Box-folder 111/3)
    - Cookbooks (Box-folder 111/4)
    - Cookies (Box-folder 111/5)
    - Cooking (General) (Box-folder 111/6)
    - Creameries (Box-folder 111/7)
    - Eggs (Box-folder 111/8)
    - Food Dehydration (Box-folder 111/9)
    - Food Drives (Box-folder 111/10)
    - Food Inspections (Box-folder 111/11)
    - Food Preservation (Box-folder 111/12)
    - Frozen Food (Box-folder 111/13)
    - Groceries and Grocery Stores (Box-folder 111/14)
    - Gum (Box-folder 111/15)
    - Horsemeat (Box-folder 111/16)
    - Ice Cream (Box-folder 111/17)
    - Liquor (Box-folder 111/18)
    - Loaves & Fishes Program (Box-folder 111/19)
    - Lutefisk (Box-folder 111/20)
    - Meat (Box-folder 111/21)
    - Meat Markets (Box-folder 111/22)
    - Surplus Food (Box-folder 111/23)
  - Food Stamps (Box-folder 111/24)
  - Foreign Sailors (Box-folder 111/25)
  - Forest (Unidentified) (Box-folder 111/26)
    Image of a car parked in a forest with the caption, "In the park like yellow pine forest."
  - Forest Fires and Firefighting (1) (Box-folder 111/27)
  - Forest Fires and Firefighting (2) (Box-folder 112/1)
  - Forestry, Subseries 11
    - Aerial Logging (Box-folder 112/2)
    - Cone Picking (Box-folder 112/3)
    - Flumes (Box-folder 112/4)
    - Forest Management (Box-folder 112/5)
    - Forest Science Laboratory (Box-folder 112/6)
    - Log Branding (Box-folder 112/7)
    - Log Jams (Box-folder 112/8)
    - Log Salvage (Box-folder 112/9)
    - Log Transportation (1) (Box-folder 112/10)
      Contains photos of logs being moved by log rafts, horse teams, ox teams, trains, and trucks.
    - Log Transportation (2) (Box-folder 112/11)
    - Logging (1) (Box-folder 112/12)
    - Logging (2) (Box-folder 112/13)
    - Logging Conferences (Box-folder 112/14)
    - Logging Equipment and Machinery (Box-folder 112/15)
    - Lookout Stations (Box-folder 112/16)
    - Lumber (Box-folder 112/17)
    - Lumber Mills (Box-folder 112/18)
    - Mill Ponds (Box-folder 112/19)
    - Notched Lumber (Box-folder 112/20)
    - Seeding (Box-folder 112/21)